Global persistent infrared surveillance continues to be a critical national security space mission.
全球持久性红外监视仍然是一项重要的国家安全空间任务
The Cold War focus on strategic ICBM systems has expanded
冷战时期对战略洲际弹道导弹系统的关注已经扩展到
to include short and mid-range ballistic missile threats.
包括短程和中程弹道导弹威胁
The defense support program maintains the legacy Cold War monitoring
国防支持计划保持了冷战时期的监测
to warn of ICBM missile launches against the US.
以警告针对美国的洲际弹道导弹发射
The replacement programs, the Space-Based InfRared System or SBIRS
替代计划 即天基红外系统或SBIRS
which is already provided to infrared sensor payloads in Highly Elliptical Orbits or HEO.
已经提供给高椭圆轨道或HEO上的红外传感器有效载荷
The SBIRS program is also deploying multiple spacecraft into Geosynchronous Earth Orbit or GEO.
SBIRS计划也正在将多个航天器部署到地球同步轨道或GEO
Each has two independent infrared sensors.
每个都有两个独立的红外传感器
One is a scanner dedicated to missile warning with full earth monitoring.
一个是专门用于导弹预警的扫描仪 对地球进行全面监测
The other sensor is a taskable starer that can focus on selected regions.
另一个传感器是一个可执行任务的跟踪器 可以聚焦于选定的区域
Each pair of sensors act simultaneously and independently of each other
每对传感器同时独立工作
providing a robust castable infrared platform.
提供了一个强大的可投射的红外平台
SBIRS is the nation's next generation of space-based infrared surveillance.
SBIRS是国家的下一代天基红外监视
The program has already proven its value with successful HEO payloads on orbit.
该计划已经用成功的HEO有效载荷在轨道上证明了其价值
With deployment of the GEO spacecraft, SBIRS will be an unprecedented resource
随着地球同步轨道航天器的部署 SBIRS将成为一种前所未有的资源
as the nation's global taskable and persistent infrared monitoring sentinel.
作为国家的全球可执行任务和持久的红外监测哨兵 将成为一种前所未有的资源